travelsort.com 2011-03-19

# TravelSort

TravelSort Privacy Policy

TravelSort has provided this Privacy Policy because we value your right to privacy. Please read it to learn more about the information TravelSort collects and how that information is used. By visiting the TravelSort Web site, you are accepting the Privacy Policy.

TravelSort’s Privacy Policy covers TravelSort’s treatment of personal information that TravelSort gathers while you are on the TravelSort Web site and when you use TravelSort services. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that TravelSort does not control, or to individuals not employed or managed by TravelSort.

TravelSort’s goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with highly personalized, relevant travel advice, recommendations and exclusive deals. We only collect personal information that is relevant to this goal.

TravelSort collects personally identifying information during the registration and profile creation process, including name, email, gender, location, travel preferences, etc. TravelSort also may collect and store additional preference information, for example via quizzes, surveys, feedback and emails, to improve its recommendations to users and for internal research purposes. TravelSort may also aggregate data across all users in order to determine and target demographics for marketing and advertising purposes.

We may use your personal information to periodically contact you with news or important information from TravelSort, to provide you with other information or invitations related to your membership or the TravelSort community, and to request your feedback on our site. In addition to these periodic updates, we may email you additional materials, but only if you specifically request them. These might include opt-in newsletters, alerts, and other materials that you proactively request from TravelSort.

Your profile on TravelSort will be publicly viewable and identifiable via your screen name, consisting of your first name and the first initial of your last name. Your profile will include your travel and preference data, such as your favorite cities, types of hotels you prefer to stay in, etc. You may opt not to provide a complete profile, although this may prevent us from providing relevant travel recommendations to you and may make you ineligible for certain exclusive deals and promotions.

TravelSort will not share your email address with any other members or third parties without your consent, nor display it any public manner. TravelSort may share aggregated user demographics and preference data for marketing and advertising purposes.

If you object to the uses listed above for any reason, you may cancel your TravelSort account by simply logging into your account and selecting “cancel my account.” We will send you an e-mail to confirm your request. After we receive confirmation, we will remove your profile information from our active database, but content that you have submitted to the site will remain, although it won’t be attributed to your name, and some of your profile information may remain in our archives.

If you do not register, then we will be unable to personalize your experience, you may not be able to use all site functions, and the information we collect from you is limited. We log your IP address in order to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our Web site and track usage statistics.

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our Web site are visited and by how many people.

If you register, we may store all or some of the information you provide us in a cookie file on your hard drive, so that our system will recognize you each time you visit our site. In that way, we can save your preferences from visit to visit and present you with a customized Web site, without requiring you to log into our site every time you visit.

If you don’t register with us, the cookies that we use contain no personally identifiable information that would allow us to identify you. Cookies cannot be used to read data off of your hard drive, and cannot retrieve information from any other cookies created by other Web sites. We use cookies to help us understand how visitors use our site, and to help us to improve our site.

Information about our users and their travel preferences is crucial to our business of providing the personalized and relevant travel recommendations. We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone. We share your personal information only as follows:

Protection of TravelSort and others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a subpoena or other legal process; prevent a legal violation; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of TravelSort, our employees, our users, or others.

With your consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your personal information may be shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and you will be able to prevent the sharing of this information by opting out.

Your TravelSort account is protected by a password for your privacy and security. Please carefully protect your account credentials to prevent unauthorized access to your account.

TravelSort provides links to other sites with valuable travel products, services and advice. We are not responsible for any content on these sites, or their privacy policies. Please consult these sites directly for any questions you may have about them.

This Web site is a general audience site, and we do not knowingly collect information about children. No one under age 13 is allowed to use the site, provide any personal information or receive our emails. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s)or legal guardian(s) before viewing the TravelSort Web site or receiving emails.

If you wish to stop receiving emails from TravelSort, please click on the unsubscribe link in any TravelSort email. You will be shown a confirmation page; after you click on the confirm link you will be unsubscribed. You may also unsubscribe by emailing your request to [unsubscribe@travelsort.com](mailto:unsubscribe@travelsort.com)

By visiting the TravelSort Web site, your visit and all privacy issues are subject to this Privacy Policy and TravelSort’s Terms of Use.

TravelSort reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy from time to time; updates will be posted to this page, together with the date of the most recent modification. Please note that if you continue to use TravelSort.com, this will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions or concerns about TravelSort’s Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@travelsort.com](mailto:privacy@travelsort.com).

Last modified: September 2, 2010
